The Christmas Checklist is a tv movie, comedy,
romance film directed by Anne De Léan.
A grieving daughter discovers a red envelope from her mom that contains a final request: for her to complete
a Christmas Checklist of twelve activities before Christmas, the last one being “Find Love”.
Emily Robertson, played by Sarah Power.
Noah Carver, played by Jarod Joseph.
Knox Catalina 'Kat', played by Monica Rodriguez.
Isaiah, played by Dakota Jamal Wellman.
Nick, played by Alain Goulem.
Mary Masters, played by Laura Mitchell.
The Adventure of the Christmas Pudding and a Selection of Entrées is a short story collection written by
Agatha Christie and first published in the UK by the Collins Crime Club on 24 October 1960.
It is the only Christie first edition published in the UK that contains stories with both
Hercule Poirot and Miss Marple, the writer's two most famous detectives.
It retailed in the UK for twelve shillings and
sixpence (12/6) and comprises six cases.
It was not published in the US although the stories it
contains were published in other volumes there.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.